2carpros.com 2017-03-04

# Privacy Policy

2CarPros has a firm commitment to the privacy of our visitors. Because the World Wide Web allows a level of information exchange not previously possible with other media, we believe it is important for our visitors to understand how our website collects information and how that information is used. Our primary goal is to make each visit to 2CarPros satisfying, productive and easy for you. In order to do this, we use information you provide to create a personalized online experience that anticipates the kinds of services and information you need.

Depending on the service you access, you could be asked to provide your name, e-mail address, information about your car, information about what you like or do not like, and other information specific to certain features available at 2CarPros. This information helps us better serve you in many different ways. While we are working hard to create a website that is easy to use and anticipates your needs, we also want all of our visitors to be able to control their privacy. Therefore, the following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

 **Your IP address**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to help identify you on specific parts of the site, such as 2CarPros, and to gather broad demographic information.

**Information we collect from you**

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (their name and e-mail address).  This information is never available for anyone outside of 2CarPros.com

**Our web partners**

To provide you with the best selection of services and content, this site contains links to many other sites. 2CarPros is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other third party website. If you visit any of those websites, please read their privacy statement to learn how they may use the information they gather from you.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We value the information our visitors and member service centers share with us as a trust in our care, and pledge to protect that information with all reasonable measures.

**Disclaimer**

The information found in the 2Carpros.com website is not intended to replace the advice of your automobile mechanic and is not a substitute for a thorough diagnostic inspection by a qualified professional mechanic. No vehicle repair should be attempted without a thorough knowledge of the mechanics of the repair and the risks involved. The purpose of this website is to educate and inform. No claim or guarantee is intended to the accuracy of the information on this site although every attempt has been made to verify the accuracy of all information with the exception of the pubic forum.

**Cookies and Similar Technology**

We use 'cookie' technology to collect data regarding your visits to the 2CarPros Network. This data is stored in aggregate form and is not used to identify any particular user or individual. We use cookies and similar tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: Users can either disable cookies via their browser or opt out via the Network Advertising site using browser settings.

  * Keeping count of your return visits to the 2CarPros Network or our Affiliates', Advertisers' or partners' sites;
  * Accumulating and reporting aggregate, statistical information in connection with the 2CarPros Network;
  * Determining which features users like best; and
  * Saving your User ID or other information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the 2CarPros Network.

Although we may track the numbers of visitors to inform us on how best to improve and update the 2CarPros Network and enhance the experience for all visitors, Personal information is not extracted in this process. We use tracking information on an aggregated basis to help us operate the 2CarPros Network, enhance and improve our service, improve the look of the 2CarPros Network and display advertising and marketing information.

We may also use third parties to display or serve advertising on the 2CarPros Network and our web-based newsletters or other communications which you may choose to receive. Often these third party Advertisers employ cookie and web bug technologies to measure advertising effectiveness. You should be aware that different rules might apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your information by third parties in connection with their advertisements, promotions and other websites you encounter on the Internet. The use of such technology by these third parties is within their control and not ours. Even if we have a relationship with the third party, we do not control those sites or their policies and practices regarding your information. This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of Personal Information that an Advertiser or ad server may collect from you. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions directly of them in this regard.

**Privacy of Your Postings**

We respect the privacy of the contents of users' e-mail and Postings. However, we reserve the right to monitor or edit information pertaining to any e-mail or Posting or its contents to a third party, if we believe such action is required by law or is necessary to protect and defend our rights, to enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use, or to protect the interests of our users, Affiliates, Advertisers, suppliers, service providers and others.

 **Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) to help analyse the use of this website. For this purpose, Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer. 

2CarPros will not use, and will not allow any third party to use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to this site. Google may transfer the information collected by Google Analytics to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. According to Google Analytics terms of service, Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. 

By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you in the manner and for the purposes set out above. You may refuse the use of cookies by downloading and installing [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js) to indicate that information about the website visit should not be sent to Google Analytics. 

This website also uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. You can op-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by clicking on the following [link](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

 **Contact**

If you have any question or comments about 2CarPros please [contact us](http://www.2carpros.com/contacts/new)
